dropshipblueprint.com 2011-11-01

# Dropship Blueprint Privacy Policy

Dropship Blueprint Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on every page of our site.

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Dropship Blueprint website. On some pages, you can place orders, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

Name   
Email address   
Password  
(etc.) 

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

We do not share any of your personal information with suppliers offering the [product lines](http://www.dropshipblueprint.com/sitemap/products) and/or [brand names](http://www.dropshipblueprint.com/sitemap/brands) contained in our directory. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract children.

You can access all of your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us via email or phone. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us at service[at]dropshipblueprint.com.
